Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs, ca. 1950s-2007 AIS.2013.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Negatives, ca. 1950s-2000; I.
  - 120mm Negatives, ca. 1950s-1999; 2.
    - 1975
      - Koppers: Jack Nicklaus, Golf, Columbus, Ohio, October 1, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 12-16)
      - Koppers: Jack Nicklaus, Columbus, Ohio, October 8, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 17-19)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), Iriax Dome, October 17, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 20-22)
      - Koppers, October 17, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 24-35)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, Harmarville, Rehab Center, October 21, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 37-39)
      - Koppers, October 21, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 40-42)
      - Koppers, October 27, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 47-51)
      - Koppers, November 20, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 53-56)
      - Koppers, November 20, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 59-65)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), N.C.X., Virginia, December 2, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 68-81)
    - 1976
      - Pipe Building, February 3, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 15-17)
      - Koppers: Res. Frances, March 1, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 22-32)
      - Koppers, March 1, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 33-48)
      - Koppers, April 8, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 54-56)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, April 15, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 60-66)
      - Koppers: N.C.X. Shakes and Laminated Bridges, April 15, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 67)
      - Koppers: N.C.X. Shakes and Laminated Bridges, April 15, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 68-77)
      - Koppers, April 27, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 78)
      - Koppers, May 5, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 3-10)
      - Koppers, May 10, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 11-17)
      - Koppers: Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), Chicago and Columbian Wood, May 10, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 21-29)
      - Koppers: Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), Outdoor Wood and KMM, May 30, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 30-35)
      - Koppers, May 30, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 36-38)
      - Gateway #2, June 15, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 39-40)
      - Koppers, August 2, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 42-63)
      - Koppers, August 9, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 67-72)
      - Wood Construction, August 25, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 3-6)
      - Koppers, August 30, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 7-10)
      - Koppers: Wood Things, September 5, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 11-20)
      - Coke Owen Model, September 10, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 21-22)
      - Koppers, September 10, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 23-24)
      - Koppers, September 25, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - Koppers Manufacturing, September 27, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 41-43)
      - Koppers, October 27, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 45, 48)
      - Koppers: Weirton Coke Plant, October 27, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 49-50)
      - Koppers: Theim Co., November 19, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 53)
      - Koppers, November 19, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 54-57)
      - Koppers: Robert Kohler, November 16, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 58-62)
      - Robert Kohler, Lando, Marion Power Shovel, December 8, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 67-69)
      - Koppers: Barb Portrait, December 12, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 72-73)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, December 13, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 74-76)
      - Koppers: Robert Kohler, December 17, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 77-83)
    - 1977
      - Robert Kohler, Heritage Award, Charlotte North Carolina, January 19, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Koppers, February 7, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 4-6)
      - Downing Advertising, Ionics, Inc., February 15, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Koppers: Huck, Cox Wood Treatment, Orangeburg South Carolina, April 24, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 18-33)
      - Koppers, June 24, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 45-49)
      - Koppers, June 29, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 51-52)
      - Koppers, August 10, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 53-57)
      - Robert Kohler, August 15, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 62-67, 69)
      - Koppers, September 21, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1-6)
      - Koppers: Titus Products, Houston Texas, December 2, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 27-32)
      - Koppers: Cumberland Circle, December 8, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 33-37, 40-48)
      - Koppers, September 20, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 40-45)
      - Koppers: Lander and Sprout, October 2, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 46-48, 52-55)
      - Robert Kohler, October 12, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 49)
      - Robert Kohler, October 13, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 50-52)
      - Koppers: Sentry Insurance Building, October 25, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 59-60, 66-71)
    - 1978
      - Koppers, January 9, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Koppers: N.C.X. Wood, February 15, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 14-22)
      - Koppers: Rail Wood Sawmill, March, 3 1978 (Box 37, Folder 26-29)
      - Koppers: Houston, Dallas, April 12, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 34-44)
      - Koppers: Outdoor Wood Display, May 15, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 67-68)
      - Koppers: Pensacola, Florida, May 24, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 69-86)
      - Koppers: Chicken Coops, July 19, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 1-4)
      - The White Hawk Sailboat, July 24, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 7-13)
      - Koppers: Florida Projects, December 18, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 19-25)
    - 1979
      - Koppers, August 29, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 45-54)
    - 1980
      - Koppers, January 25, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 2-23)
      - Koppers: Montreal, Canada, May 23, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 9-22)
    - 1982
      - Koppers: Washington Plaza, Woman on Roof of Building, July 28, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - 1991
      - Hickson Corporation: Perfect Pine Tree, August 28, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 67)
    - 1993
      - Hickson Corporation, September 24, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 21-25)
      - Hickson Corporation, October 26, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 33-37)
    - 1996
      - Hickson Corporation, August 23, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1-5)
    - 1998
      - Hickson Corporation, September 11, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 28-31)
    - 1999
      - Hickson Corporation, October 1, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - Undated
      - Maria's Painting (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Pitt Church Bulletin Board (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - David Saltzman's Son (Box 1, Folder 32-37)
      - Valery Test Roll (Mat on Toy Bike) (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Namir: Safety Medicine Cabinet (Box 1, Folder 46-47)
      - Painting at Pitt; Pile of Dirt in a Quarry (Box 1, Folder 73)
      - Levinson Steel (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Koppers: All Wood Foundation, Church (Box 2, Folder 24-35)
      - Woman Sitting Outside (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - Undated Negatives (Box 47, Folder 75)
      - Koppers: Stone Quarry (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - 4x5 Negatives, 1970-1974; 3.
    - Koppers, October 26, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Steinberg House and Peter, February 21, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Koppers: Meadows Stable, June 3, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Koppers: Fletcher L. Byrom, July 8, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Sempeon Deck, October 25, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Gym and Swimming Pool, September 25, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Koppers: Linn Noah, April 5, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Koppers: Weirton Coke Plant, May 11, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Koppers: Robert O'Gara, July 20, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Koppers: Roof Tar, August 21, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Koppers: Wood Deck, October 19, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Railroad Tracks, October 3, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Koppers: Wood, November 12, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Koppers, August 30, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Koppers: Linn Noah, Steak and Ale, Fire Proof Plywood, Atlanta, Georgia, May 1, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Koppers: Jack Nicklaus, Golf, Columbus, October 1, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Bob Kohler, October 12, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Gus Porter (Kilts), Walnut and Locust (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Swimming Pool (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Social Security Administration: Kids at Door, Beckley, West Virginia, ca. 1960s/1970s (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Lumber Yard; Thrift Drug Classic, Interior with Pool,; Interior with Pool and People, ca. 1990s (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Bud and Maria, ca. 1960s/1970s (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Pitt: Posvar (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Fireworks at the Point (Box 47, Folder 46)
    - Mrs. Evans (Box 47, Folder 57)
    - Magee Women's Hospital: Exterior Views (Box 47, Folder 67)
    - City and Fireworks, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - "3 Black Boys Profile", September 1, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - Koppers: Swimming Pool, September 25, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 44)
      Other negatives stored in negative boxes.
    - Carnegie International, Man and Boys on Northside, Boy on Hill, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Prints and Negatives, ca. 1950s-2004; II.
  Images in this series are arranged in their original order and have been kept with their corresponding materials and arranged according to date. Those with no date have been put at the end of the series.
  - Special Topics, 1.
    Many of these topics and images can be found elsewhere in the collection, but this group has been left in the original order created by Harris to preserve his interpretation of his life's work. This subseries begins with a large group of University of Pittsburgh photographs (marked with UP and a job number), including work from Pitt Magazine. Topics also include: Carnegie Museum of Art, Hospital Council of Western Pennsylvania, Fallingwater, Peter Berndtson, Frick Fine Arts, Posvar, Bernie Kobosky, Medical World News, St. Peter's Child Development Center, John and Teresa Heinz, Heinz Annual Meeting, Race Across America, Litchfield, Sue Doyle, Heinz Chapel, Time Magazine, Fraternities and Sororities, Mademoiselle Magazine, Arnold Palmer, Europe, Gateway, Hawk's Nest, Harbison Walker, Hill District, Judy Parker, Gog Magog and Babylon, Kodalith, KDKA, Parkway Construction, Alan Greenspan, Alcoa, Panther Hollow, BMX, PPG, and J&L Steel.
    - UP-121, August 1, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      Subjects include: Trees Pool, Pitt Magazine, Cathedral of Learning, Cathedral Lawn, and Hurry-Up Scholar.
    - UP-124, April 12, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      Subjects include: Pitt Football Game vs. UCLA: Litchfield and Actor James Franciscus Cheering; Mazurek, Sue and Franciscus; and Mazurek.
    - UP-128: Pitt Campus Scenes, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - UP-129: Pitt Stadium, Home Schedule, and Campus Scenes, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      Subjects include:
    - UP-130: Pitt Campus Scenes and Cathedral of Learning, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - UP-132: Pitt Buildings, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - UP-133: Pitt Campus Scenes, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - UP-134: Cathedral Banquet, December 7, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - UP-136: Cathedral Banquet, December 7, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - UP-139, March 27, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      Subjects include: Pitt Graduation; Mrs. Litchfield with Portraits of Vice Chancellors and J&L Cleveland Rolling Mill.
    - UP-140: Chancellor Edward Harold Litchfield in House, March 30, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - UP-141, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      Subjects include: Pitt Magazine: African American Girl and Book, African American Boy and Gun; Peter Gray in Lounge Chair/ David Halliday Against a Bookshelf; Gonzalez Asenjo: Associate Professor of Math and Composer of Concert for Wind Instruments; James Joyce Scholar David Halliday; "Romeo Boy"; Alivia Cohen: "Moon Expert" Department of Earth and Planetary Science; "Sinners Will Burn" Pablo Casals Sign; Signs in Hill District; Peter Gray: First Andrey Avinoff Professor of Biology at Pitt; Frank Whittemore Wadsworth: Dean of Humanities; Panther Hollow; Signs for the neighborhoods of Oakland, Polish Hill, Southside, and Hill District.
    - UP-142: Frick Fine Arts, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - UP-143, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      Subjects include: USIA Washington: Leonard Mark "Who Speaks for the USA"; Parkway Scenes; and Former US Post Master General John A. Gronauski.
    - UP-144: Chancellor Edward Harold Litchfield at Home, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - UP-148, 1964, 1965, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 16)
      Subjects include: PITT VIPs; VIPs and a Vice Chancellor; Christmas at Pitt; Don Brockett and Joe Negri on Stage #33a Dinner at Cathedral of Learning; Pitt Basketball Game and Coach; Engineering/Mechanical Testing Lab and Dr. Henry T. Bahnson at Home.
    - UP-149: Coach Micheloson TV Interview/ Football Team, ca. 1960s (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - UP-150: Omar Khayyam More, Innovative Teacher, ca. 1960s (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Pitt Magazine, 1963-1964 (Box 78, Folder 19-23, 26)
      Subjects include: Campus Scenes; Campus Architecture; Beach Boys Concert in Pitt Sports Stadium; New Dorms/ Foreign Students; Children on Jungle Gym; New Students at Sign-In Desk; Student Party at Trees Pool; New Students Moving into Dorms; Musicians at Student Party at Trees Pool; Students in Food Line; Students at Outside Table at Night with Dorms Lit Up; Dr. Katsoyannis; Pitt Football Game; Students Inside Dorms; J&L Steel Mill, Southside, Pitt over Panther Hollow; Dr. Chinitz/Appalachian Plane, WVA Charleston Convention Center, Appalachian Plan Discussion with Dr. Chinitz; Dr. Chinitz and FDR Jr.; Dr. "Cam" Moses"; Cam Moses, Joe Colangelo, Murray "Buzzy" Susser; Building Construction by Swimming Pool; Magee Women's Hospital; Clapp Hall; IBM Computer 1620; Cityscape; Zsa Zsa Gabor; Fred Smith; Panther Hollow; Marshall Goldberg; Flag at Half-mast for JFK; Louise Bell; Oakland Corporation; Christmas at the Cathedral of Learning; Center for Regional Studies; Virgil Cantini; Jamie Van Trump; Esther Kitzes in Studio; Fritz Goro; Agnes Starrett; Frick Fine Arts Dedication; Early Computer Demo and Computers on the Top Floor of the Cathedral of Learning.
    - Pitt Graduation: Sargent Shriver, Mayor Barr and Governor Scranton, June 6, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Pitt Magazine: Children and the University, June 1, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 25)
      Subjects include: Children; Doctors; University of Pittsburgh Alumni and Cathedral of Learning.
    - Pitt Sports, September 21, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 27)
      Subjects include: Fred Mazurek (Quarterback for Pittsburgh Panthers); Sue Michelosen (Daughter of Head Coach) and John Michelosen (Head Coach).
    - Carnegie Museum of Art: Carnegie International Judges, October 13, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Carnegie Museum of Art: Carnegie International Spectators, October 30, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Pitt Campus with Telephoto Lens, June 6, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Hospital Council of Western Pennsylvania (W.P.A): Portraits of Steve Seiverts, February 15, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - Fallingwater, September 17, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - Magee Annual Report, September 30, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - ACLD: Children with Learning Disabilities, February 20, 1971, April 3, 1971, April 17, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 34-36)
    - Peter Berndtson's Show at Frick Fine Arts, April 18, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 37)
      Also includes images of Stan Marshall House and the Peter Berndtson House.
    - Pitt: Home for Crippled Children, 1971-1972 (Box 78, Folder 38, 42, 44, 47-49)
    - Pitt: Home for Crippled Children, Hubert Humphrey, June 7, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - Pitt: Bernie Kobosky, July 16, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - Pitt: Posvar Portraits, August 16, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Koppers: Octagon School, November 11, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Virgil Cantini Mural and Pierre Soulages Mural at Oliver Plaza, December 29, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Pitt Commencement: Mayor Barr, Governor Lawrence and Litchfield, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 45)
    - Pitt Graduation, April 30, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - Medical World News: Dr. Ray Greco, October 19, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 50)
    - Koppers: Al Capone, ca. 1970s (Box 78, Folder 51)
    - St. Peter's Child Development Center: Kids in Pool, July 10, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 52)
    - John and Teresa Heinz and Posvar Family, March 3, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 53)
    - Koppers: Robert O'Gara, Swanson Lumber in British Columbia, Canada, November 20, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 54)
    - Pitt: Oakland and Forbes at Night, May 14, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 55)
    - Pitt: Campus Scenes, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 56-57)
    - Heinz Annual Meeting, September 10, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 58)
    - Koppers: Employee Annual Report, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 59-60, 62-64)
    - Pitt: Learning Problems, Rita Silverman, February 11, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 61)
    - Pitt Graduation, April 30, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 65)
    - Business Week Assignment, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 66-71)
    - Walt Disney World, February 27, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 72)
    - Jimmy O'Brien at WACC, August 18, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 73)
    - Pittsburgh Youth Symphony Orchestra, ca. 1990s (Box 78, Folder 74)
    - Jitney, Lobby Display for August Wilson Play in Hill District, April 20, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 75)
    - Clean Air Car: Race Across America, February 23, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 76)
    - Pitt Magazine: Murray "Buzzy" Susser, January, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Executive Portraits, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Pitt Magazine: City Scenes, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Portraits of Litchfield, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Pitt: Litchfield Tower Dorms Under Construction, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Pitt: Homecoming Queen, Football and Litchfield, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Sue Doyle, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Pitt: Deans, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Pitt: Dean's Portraits and Panther Hollow Project, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Pitt: Christmas in Commons Room, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Heinz Chapel, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Fred Smith and Paul, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Chancellor Edward Harold Litchfield Press Conference, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Time Magazine: Dr. Klaus Hoffman, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Pitt: Children and the University, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 15-16)
    - Pitt: Cathedral of Learning and Chancellor Edward Harold Litchfield Plane, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Han Yo, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Pitt: Students in Biology Lab, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Father Walsh in Heinz Chapel, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Pitt: Campus Candids, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Sue Doyle, Cathedral of Learning, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Pitt Magazine: Dr. "Cam" Moses, December 4, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Mademoiselle Magazine at Pitt Fashion Shoot, Cathedral of Learning, Students, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Pitt: Fraternities and Sororities, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Oakland Corporation, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - "Miss Pitt" Sheila Rinne and Richard Grandy, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Pitt: Chancellor Edward Harold Litchfield and Vice Chancellors, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Bud's Family, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Civic Arena, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Carnegie Mellon University, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Gog, Magog and Babylon: Movie Stills, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Arnold Palmer at U.S. Open: Oakmont Country Club, Scores displayed in Kaufmann's Window, ca. 1960s/1970s (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Congressman William Moorhead (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Europe, ca. 1970s (Box 79, Folder 35-36)
    - Gateway, ca. 1970s (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Harbison Walker, 1972-1973 (Box 79, Folder 38-39)
    - Hawk's Nest, ca. 1969 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Hazelwood Girls and Railroad Tracks, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Hill District, ca. 1950s (Box 79, Folder 42)
      Subjects include: Building ruins; Birmingham bridge; Forbes Avenue; Kids in Schoolyard.
    - J&L Steel, ca.1960s-1970s (Box 79, Folder 43)
      Subjects include: Hazelwood Cold Rolling; Ladle Burst at Harbison Walker; Research Labs and Hot Metal.
    - Judy Parker, May 1968 (Box 79, Folder 44)
      Subjects include: New York; Eye Magazine; Barry Slelzer Studio and Mellon Park.
    - Kids in Cemetery, 1963-1964 (Box 79, Folder 45)
      Subjects include: "Gravedigger's Children"; US Department of Health and Human Services and Appalachia USA. Some of this work was made for Pitt Magazine.
    - Kodalith, ca. 1960s/1970s (Box 79, Folder 46)
    - Folder of Maria, ca. 1960s/1970s (Box 79, Folder 47)
    - Mobile Reporter for KDKA Mike Levine; Motocross at Three Rivers Stadium, ca. 1960s-1980s (Box 79, Folder 48)
    - Ketchum Advertising, ca. 1950s-1960s (Box 79, Folder 49)
    - New York Street Scenes; Dave Milton at Home, May 1968 (Box 79, Folder 50)
    - Parkway Construction, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 51)
      Subjects include: Art Swiden Boxer Training; Women at Fruit Market; Building the Parkway and Trains.
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 52)
      Subjects include: Campus Scenes; Cathedral of Learning; Litchfield Sculpture; Wayne and Julie; Downtown over J&L Plant; Horses in Schenley Park; Pitt Football Game; Frick Fine Arts Building; Forbes Field; Dollar Bank; Dr. Ariel, Chancellor and Mrs. Litchfield.
    - Alan Greenspan at Alcoa, December 15, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 53)
    - Panther Hollow; Parkway (4 Mile Run and J&L), Cathedral of Learning Stained Glass with Marcia, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 54)
    - Panther Hollow; Chancellor Edward Harold Litchfield with Model, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 55)
    - Pete Flaherty in Pittsburgh BMX Parade, ca. 1960s-1970s (Box 79, Folder 56)
    - Peter, Paul and Mary at Stanley Theater, November 1969 (Box 79, Folder 57)
    - Pitt Magazine: Annual Student Issue Cover, July 1964 (Box 79, Folder 58)
    - Pitt: Rally for Chancellor Edward Harold Litchfield, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 59)
    - Posvar, Westmoreland, Ridgeway, Barr, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 60)
    - PPG, April 1963 (Box 79, Folder 61)
    - P. and D. Saltzman at the Zoo, 7th Street Bridge, ca. 1960s (Box 79, Folder 62)
    - Ryna Statue, ca. 1950s/1960s (Box 79, Folder 63)
    - Simma, ca. 1950s/1960s (Box 79, Folder 64)
    - Special Collection (Box 79, Folder 65)
      Subjects include: Point Park; Tumi; Steppenwolf; Panther Hollow; Greenfield; Arthur Aronson; J&L Steel; Smithfield Bridge; Church of Ascension; PPG Chemical Plant; Oakland; Social Security Administration; Europe and Parkway Construction.
    - Topical (Box 79, Folder 66-69)
      Subjects include: Irish Parade; Mayor Barr; Diane Litman; Larry D'Arcy; Bruno Sammartino; Penn Camera; Judy Ross; Lou Schmidt; Benny Spiegle; Colangolo Baby; Emil and Kyp; Paul Schwartz; Newman Schmidt; Dave Milton; Tony Dodd; Mary Rita; Turtle Creek; Museum Visitors; Montefiore; Family Portrait; Portraits; Sports; and Pittsburgh Neighborhood Scenes.
    - Washington, D.C. (Box 79, Folder 72)
    - Copy Negatives (Box 79, Folder 73)
  - Early Career, ca. 1950s; 2.
    These images are from Harris's early career, focusing primarily on the mid to late 1950s. Many of the prints and negatives also have the date "November 3, 1991" which could have been a later printing or organization date. These photographs were created in the 1950s, and not 1991. Since this is the date given by Harris, it has not been changed. Though there are prints and negatives that could fit into other series in the collection, they have been kept together here to maintain original order. These images are credited to "Forest Harris."
    - Pearl, Bunny at 5th Avenue House, November 3, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 1-9)
    - Boxers/Park, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 10-15)
    - Portraits, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 16-27)
    - Howard Skippy Green, Hosea Chapman, December 20, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Photo Maxima, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 29-40, 82)
    - Portraits, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 41-50)
    - Jacki Fine, Darlington Road, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 51-57, 81)
    - Portraits/Park, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 58-70)
    - Portraits (Box 50, Folder 71, 73, 75, 80)
    - Rolleiflex 3.5 Camera Manual, ca. 1950s/1960s (Box 50, Folder 72)
    - Still Life (Box 50, Folder 74)
    - T.V. Guide (Box 50, Folder 76)
    - Portraits, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 76)
    - Howard Skippy Green, December 20, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 77)
    - Hosea Chapman, December 20, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 78)
    - Hosea Chapman: 8x10 Copy Negative, December 20, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 79)